A Guide to the WLR Foods digital records, 1948-2002 (bulk 1984-2000)
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Meetings and Minutes, 1970-2001, bulk 1985-2000, (157 items)
  - WLR Foods, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Minutes [Confidential], October 25 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. Board of Directors Meeting Minutes [Confidential], October 26 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1992
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 1992
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, June 1992
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, September 1992
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, November 1992
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, December 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1993
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 1993
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, April 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, June 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, August 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, October 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, November 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, November 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, December 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, December 1993
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, December 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Meeting Results, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy Corrections, 1994
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, January 1994-March 1994
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, March 1994-June 1994
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, May 1994
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, August 1994
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management & Board decisions, October 1994
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, October 1994
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, November 1994
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, December 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Board of Directors Meeting, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Special Board of Directors Meeting, 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, January 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, March 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, May 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, August 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, August 1995
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, October 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1996
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, June 1996
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, October 1996
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, October 1996
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, December 1996
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, December 1996
  - Minutes of Directors Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, December 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1997
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, January 1997
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, March 1997
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, March 1997
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, March 1997
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, March 1997
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, April 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. Annual Shareholder's Meeting [Confidential], October 26 1991
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, November 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1998
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 1998
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, April 1998
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, May 1998
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, June 1998
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, July 1998
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Board Organizational Meeting, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Meeting of Shareholders Proxy, 1999
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, January 1999
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, October 1999
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, October 1999
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, November 1999
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, January 2000
  - Minutes of Director's Meetings, including many management and Board decisions, February 2000
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Special Meeting of Shareholders, 2001
- Financial Reports, 1955-2000, bulk 1989-2000, (85 items)
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1955
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1956
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1957
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1958
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1959
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1960
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1961
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1962
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1963
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1964
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1965
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1966
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1967
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1968
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1969
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1970
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1971
  - Wampler-Bryan Company - Financial Statements, 1972
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Statements, 1978
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Statements, 1979
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Statements, 1980
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Statements, 1981
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Statements, 1982
  - Golden Acre Foods, Inc. -Financial Report, 1984
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Report, 1984
  - Golden Acre Foods, Inc. -Financial Report, 1985
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. -Consolidated Financial Report, 1985
  - Golden Acre Foods, Inc. -Financial Report, 1986
  - Wampler-Longacre, Inc. - Consolidated Financial Report, 1986
  - Golden Acre Foods, Inc. -Financial Report, 1987
  - Wampler-Longacre, Inc. - Consolidated Financial Report, 1987
  - Wampler-Longacre-Rockingham, Inc. - Annual Report, 1988
  - Wampler-Longacre-Rockingham, Inc. - First Quarter Results, 1988
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1989
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1989
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1989
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1990
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Results, 1990
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1990
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1990
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Report, 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Results, 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Fourth Quarter Results, 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Results, 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1991
  - Wheat Investment Banking [logo], December 19 1991
  - Wheat Investment Banking: WLR Foods, Inc. Materials prepared for the Board of Directors, December 19 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Report, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Results, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Report, 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Results, 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Fourth Quarter Results, 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Results, 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Fourth Quarter Results, 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Report, 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Report, 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Fourth Quarter Results, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Results, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Results, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Annual Report, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Results, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Results, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter Results, 2000
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Fourth Quarter Results, 2000
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Second Quarter Results, 2000
- Publications, 1979-2002, bulk 1988-2002, (67 items)
  - Company Publications, 1979
  - Company Publications, November 1984-December 1984
  - Company Publications, October 1986
  - Company Publications, 1987
  - Company Publications, December 1987
  - Company Publications, January 1988
  - Company Publications, January 1988-February 1988
  - Company Publications, March 1988-April 1988
  - Company Publications, June1988-July 1988
  - Company Publications, November 1988-January 1989
  - Company Publications, January 1989-March 1989
  - Company Publications, March 1989-May 1989
  - Company Publications, March 1989-May 1989
  - Company Publications, November 1989
  - Company Publications, November 1989
  - Company Publications, December 1990
  - Company Publications, May 1991
  - Company Publications, June 1991-August 1991
  - Company Publications, December 1991
  - Company Publications, 1992
  - Company Publications, February 1992
  - Company Publications, June 1992
  - Company Publications, February 1993
  - Company Publications, June 1993
  - Company Publications, October 1993
  - Company Publications, December 1993
  - Company Publications, January 1994-April 1994
  - Company Publications, April 1994
  - Company Publications, June 1997
  - Company Publications, October 1994
  - Company Publications, March 1995-May 1995
  - Company Publications, March 1995-May 1995
  - Company Publications, December 1995
  - Company Publications, February 1996
  - Company Publications, Jan1998-February 1998
  - Company Publications, February 1998
  - Company Publications, March 1998
  - Company Publications, September 1998
  - Company Publications, November 1998
  - Company Publications, March 1999
  - Company Publications, April 1999
  - Company Publications, June 1999
  - Company Publications, July 1999
  - Company Publications, August 1999
  - Company Publications, September 1999
  - Company Publications, October 1999
  - Company Publications, November 1999
  - Company Publications, December 1999
  - Company Publications, January 2000
  - Company Publications, February 2000
  - Company Publications, February 2000
  - Company Publications, February 2000
  - Company Publications, March 2000
  - Company Publications, April 2000
  - Company Publications, May 2000
  - Company Publications, June 2000
  - Company Publications, July 2000
  - Company Publications, August 2000
  - Company Publications, November 2000
  - Company Publications, February 2001
  - Company Publications, March 2001-May 2001
  - Company Publications, March 2002-May 2002
  - Company Publications, June 2002-August 2002
  - Company Publications, September 2002-November 2002
  - Company Publications, undated
  - Company Publications, undated
  - Company Publications, undated
- Acquisitions, Mergers, and Takeovers, 1984-2000, bulk 1984-1995, (58 items)
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, June 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, August 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, September 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, November 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, November 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, December 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, December 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, December 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, December 1984
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, April 1985
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, October 1986
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, January 1985
  - Agreement and Plan of Affiliation, December 15 1986
  - Affiliation of Wampler-Longacre & Rockingham Poultry Coop., 1987
  - Amended and Restated Affiliation Agreement, April 13 1987
  - Circuit Court of Rockingham County: Voluntary Dissolution of RPMC, Inc., September 23 1987
  - Index to financial statements, followed by the financial statements, August 14 1989-December 31 1989
  - Appendix A, Merger Agreement and Plan of Reorganization, December 14 1989
  - Appendix B, Articles of Incorporation of New ABC Inc., December 14 1989
  - Appendix C, Bylaws of New ABC Inc., December 14 1989
  - Appendix D, Article 15 of Title 13.1 of the Code of Virginia of 1950, as amended: Dissenters' Rights, December 14 1989
  - Resolutions, 1990
  - Prospectus for takeover of WLR Foods Inc. by Cassco Corporation, April 6 1990
  - Special Power of Attorney, October 26 1991
  - Buy out of Longacre's Interest, December 1991
  - Buy out of Longacre's Interest, January 1992
  - Merger with Round Hill Co., February 1993
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Foods Board Decision, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Foods Tender Offer, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Foods Tender Offer Board Decision, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Foods Tender Offer Board Decision, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Hostile Takeover Proxy, 1994
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, 1994, April 1994-May 1994
  - Cuddy Acquisition, 1994, June 1994-August 1994
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, 1994, August 1994
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, 1994, September 1994
  - Acquisition of several ice companies, November 1994
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, December 1994
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, September 1995
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, October 1995
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, October 1995
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, October 1995
  - Tyson Hostile Takeover Attempt, January 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Sale of Cassco Complete, 1998
  - Expansion of WLR into WVA, April 1999
  - Buy out of WLR by Pilgrim's Pride Inc., January 2000
  - Buy out of WLR by Pilgrim's Pride, Inc., October 2000
  - Acquisition of Several Ice Companies, undated
  - Circuit Court of Rockingham County: Voluntary Dissolution of RPMC, Inc. [Petition], undated
  - Cuddy Acquisition, undated
  - Merger Wampler Foods & Longacre, 1984, undated
  - Merger with Round Hill Co., undated
  - Preliminary Prospective Buyers, undated
  - Purchase of Cassco Ice & Cold Storage, Inc., undated
  - Spread sheet of new construction on all sites, undated
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Resolutions Approving Acquisition of Certain Assets, undated
  - Notice of "Plan of Merger", undated
- Announcements, Memos, and News, 1987-2000, bulk 1992-1999, (44 items)
  - Memo from Lawrence Hoover Jr. to W-L Board of Directors [cover letter for Amended and Restated Affiliation Agreement], April 16 1987
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Corporate Accomplishments, 1988-1990
  - WLR Foods, Job Description for Chief Operating Officer, December 20 1988
  - Notice to the Exec. Comm. About employment duties and responsibilities, February 8 1988
  - WLR Foods, Inc. Nominating Committee, October 23 1989
  - Memo: Appointment of Dr. Gene Misner as GM of Rockingham County Poultry, January 25 1989
  - News Release, February 3 1989
  - Memo concerning WLR Foods Corporate contribution program, December 19 1989
  - News Release: Strong Second Quarter and 6 month results, January 30 1990
  - Memo concerning Rockingham Poultry, Inc.'s Upgraded Rendering plant, April 16 1990
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Memo of Second Quarter Financial Statements, 1991
  - Articles of Restatement of WLR Foods, Inc., December 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. News Release, May 1 1991
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Stock Share News Release, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Round Hill Foods News Release, 1992
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Foods News Release, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Tyson Foods Tender Offer News Release, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Adoption of the Rights Plan, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Letter to Poultry Producers regarding Tyson, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Memo of Keeler's Farm Bureau Speech, 1994
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Stock Repurchase News Release, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Third Quarter Increased Earnings News Report, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Memo of New Hope Feeds Acquisition, 1995
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter News Report, 1996
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - News Release - Common Stock Dividend, etc., 1997
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Consolidating Turkey News Release, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Pending Sale of Assets News Report, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Brookshire Named VP of Administration, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Charlie Wampler Steps Down as Chairman, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Dale S. Lam named VP of Finance, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Expansion of PA Facilities, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Lam named Chief Financial Officer - 1998, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - New Credit Facility Announcement, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - William D. Wampler Elected New Chairman, 1998
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Expected Savings News Release, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - First Quarter News Report, 1999
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Pilgrim's Pride Joint Statement, 2000
  - "Rockingham's Export Experts", undated
  - "WLR Foods Selling a New Product: Itself" [DNR article], undated
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Comparison of Five-Year Cumulative Total Return, undated
  - WLR Foods, Inc. - Golden West Foods Announcement regarding NC Fa., undated
  - Advertisement for Rockingham Poultry, undated
  - DNR articles, undated
- Audit and Examination Reports, 1948-1978, bulk 1958-1978, (39 items)
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Examination, 1948
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Audit, 1953
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Audit, 1954
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Examination, 1957
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1958
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Examination, 1958
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Examination, 1958
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1959
  - Wampler Feed and Seed Company -Report on Examination, 1959
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1960
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1960
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1961
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1961
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1962
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1962
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1962
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1963
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1963
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1964
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1964
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1965
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1965
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1966
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1966
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1967
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1967
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1968
  - Wampler Feeds, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1968
  - Virginia Valley Processors, Inc. -Report on Examination, 1969
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1970
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1971
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1972
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1973
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1974
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1975
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1976
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1977
  - Wampler Foods, Inc. Report on Examination, 1978
- Various Documents, 1987-1996, bulk 1988, (22 items)
  - Time Table, 1987-1988
  - Capital Expenditure Requests, January 15 1987
  - U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, Form 10-Q, September 26 1987
  - Notice that Rockingham will be affiliated with W-L, January 4 1988
  - OTC Review, December 1988
  - U.S. Securities & Exchange Commission: Current Report, December 20 1988
  - U.S. Securities & Exchange Commission: Quarterly Report, December 31 1988
  - WLR Foods Form 10-K, 1989, 1989
  - Investment Opinion from Davenport & Co. of Va, Inc., July 15 1991
  - WLR Philosophy, April 1993
  - WLR Philosophy, November 1994
  - Wampler Foods - Name Change, 1996
  - By-Laws of Rockingham Poultry, Inc., undated
  - By-Laws of WLR, Inc., undated
  - Continuation of by-laws [see By-Laws of WLR, Inc.], as well as proposed changes to old by-laws, undated
  - Invitation to the South Eastern Poultry & Egg Association Convention, undated
  - Supplemental Deferred Compensation Agreement, undated
  - WLR Foods and the Poultry Industry, undated
  - WLR Foods Philosophy, undated
  - WLR Foods Philosophy, undated
- Correspondence, 1988-1991, (8 items)